playkissing.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy policy

Privacy Policy

Here are the privacy policy for www.playkissing.com If you need more information, please contact us in our contact form.

Google Ad Policy

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve your ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google advertising privacy policies](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Websites linking to this http://www.playkissing.com have chosen to adopt this generic privacy policy as their own. This means that they agree to abide by the principles laid out below. 

ValueClick Media Policy

Online behavioral advertising ("OBA") and/or multi-site advertising is occurring on playkissing.com We partner with ValueClick Media to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick Media may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit: <http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>.

Websites linking to this http://www.playkissing.com have chosen to adopt this generic privacy policy as their own. This means that they agree to abide by the principles laid out below. 

Cookies

We use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:   
Google Adsense  
ValueClick Media  
CPMStar  
Kitara Media  
Intergi Media 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org
